Ms. Carter,
Congratulations,
you're pregnant.
Wait, what?
Are you serious?
I...
I'm 40!
How could I be pregnant?
Well, at 40,
it's considered a high-risk pregnancy.
The baby's still in a fragile position,
so you need to be careful.
No stress,
no physical impacts.
otherwise,
there's a chance of miscarriage.
Alright,
I'll prescribe some medicine to help stabilize the pregnancy.
No,
that's okay.
I don't need it, thanks.
Mom,
I'll bring
the test results home.
I'm sorry.
You.
It's you.
Mr. Zander,
your mother's been urging you
to get married this year,
and she wants a grandkid next year.
Got it.
Mr. Zander,
the results haven't changed.
Your chances of having a child...
well,
are less than one in a million.
Mom,
I've let you down.
Your hope for a grandchild...
is not gonna happen.
I'm sorry.
What's the point of all this money
if I don't even have an heir?
Alone...
that's what I'll be.
This guy's watch
is high-end, custom-made.
It's worth at least 20 million.
If I can snag him,
I'm set for life.
That's for sure.
Here's your drink, sir.
Sir,
you look like something's bothering you.
How about
we share a drink?
Get lost.
Sir.
I'm not saying it again.
Please, Mr. Clark,  I'm begging you!
Just give me a six-month salary advance.
If I don't get the money,
my daughter
will be kicked out of school.
Please, help me.
No way!
Look at your mess.
A mom with terminal cancer
and a kid in college.
Plus,
you're always selling blood.
I don't even know
if you'll last another six months.
And if you don't?
Who's gonna pay me back?
Huh?
Me?
It won't happen, I swear.
I'll work hard, please.
Just this once,
help me.
Don't try to guilt me.
You want the job?
Do it.
If not, get out!
Mr. Clark!
Ugh, it's so hot...
Why is this drink hitting me so hard?
Sir, sorry,
I'm just here to clean.
Are you okay?
Help me...
I'll pay you.